what happened?
どうしたの?
ERROR
いい体してる
Super beautiful.
超綺麗
That's naughty.
やらしいな
ERROR
やらしすぎない?
超キョウチ
terrible.
やばい
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's so cool.
クリオッケイな
I couldn't hold it anymore.
我慢できなくなってきちゃった
What should I do?
どうしよう?
good?
いい?
ERROR
生だけどいいの?
減っちゃうよ
Why is it so tight?
なんでこんなにきついの?
It really doesn't go away.
すっごい消えない
what happened?
どうしたの?
Awesome.
すっごい
what happened?
どうしたの?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
ERROR
まだチンチン入れただけだよ
動かしてないよ
amazing
すごい
hey.
ね
It went all the way in.
奥 まで入ったね
Does it move?
動かる?
ERROR
動かしていい?
It seems dangerous though.
やばそうだけど
I'll move it.
動かすよ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
copper?
どう?
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
It's really tight.
すっごいきつい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
ERROR
おんち?
amazing.
すごい
On
おん
Chi?
ち?
Uncle?
お んち?
Onchi?
おんち?
That's amazing.
すごいね
hey
ね
picture.
え
It's tight.
ひ っついよ
Will the current run?
電流走っちゃうの?
I can't move.
動けないね
It looks like you can't move.
動けなそうだね
Awesome, amazing.
すごいすごい
Do you feel that way?
そんな感じちゃうの?
It's amazing when it hits the deep end.
奥に当たると すごいんだよね
It's hitting here, right?
ここに当たってるでしょ
Isn't it tough when it hits here?
ここに当たるときついんじゃない?
Hey.
ねえ
Look.
ほら
Hey.
ねえ
Here.
ここに
ERROR
もっとたらして
It's so delicious.
めっちゃおいしい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's in the back.
奥だ
Right here.
ここでしょ
Hey.
ね え
It's tough when you hit here, isn't it?
ここに当たるときついんでしょ
Look.
ほら
It's here.
ここだ
Put your hands behind me.
後ろに手ついてさ
Open your eyes and have an idea.
目をましてひらめてね
Can you take it in and out slowly?
ゆっくり出し入れできる?
yes.
そう
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I'm getting dizzy.
やつんまいになって
Okay.
よろしい
It feels so good.
めちゃくちゃ気持ちいい
Ah, it feels good.
あー気持ちいい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
What do you think?
どうだ?
It feels good in the mouth.
口分で気持ちいい
That's amazing.
すごいね
This is amazing.
すごいこれ
That's amazing.
すごいね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
amazing.
すごい
terrible.
やばい
Can I take it out?
出していい?
Let's go.
いくよ
Is this okay as an impression?
感想としていい?
Do you understand?
わかる?
Is it visible?
映ってる?
ERROR
静止入ってる?
Do you understand?
わかる?
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
This is how it turned out.
こんなになってるんだよ
It was amazing.
すごかったね
ERROR
震えてたよ
Did it feel good?
気 持ちよかった?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしくなっちゃった?